whats-theword.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy - 4 Pics 1 Word - What's The Word Answers

**Whats-TheWord.com, LLC. Privacy Policy**

As used in this Privacy Policy, “Whats-TheWord” refers to all websites, mobile sites, applications, and other properties or services owned or operated by Whats-TheWord.com, LLC.

By visiting Whats-TheWord, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of user information. It does not apply to the practices of companies that Whats-TheWord does not own or control, or to individuals whom Whats-TheWord does not employ or manage, including any of the third parties to which Whats-TheWord may disclose user information as set forth in this Policy.

### Information Collected by Whats-TheWord

Whats-TheWord may obtain the following types of information from you or concerning your computer or device (“Information”), which may include information that can be used to identify you as specified below (“Personally Identifiable Information”):

  * Name
  * Email
  * Blog or Website URL
  * Activities or Content Viewed on Whats-TheWord
  * Information Collected Automatically (see below)

**Information Collected Automatically**

Whats-TheWord may automatically receive and log certain types of information when you visit or interact with our websites, mobile applications or other products, including:

  * Browser Information
  * Operating System Information
  * Mobile Device Information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)
  * IP Address
  * Internet Service Provider
  * Content Viewed
  * Geographic Location
  * Connection Speed
  * Time of Visit
  * Referring Site, Application, or Service

### Whats-TheWord Use of This Information

Whats-TheWord uses the Information we obtain from or concerning you or your computer or device to manage our business, improve our offerings, and understand how users are engaging with Whats-TheWord.

### Disclosure of Information to Others and/or Third Parties

Whats-TheWord may disclose Information from or concerning you or your computer or device to others and/or to third parties in the circumstances described below. By visiting, accessing or using Whats-TheWord products or offerings, you consent to the disclosure of your Information in the manner described below. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the policies or practices of any third parties of the types mentioned below.

Some reasons for Whats-TheWord to disclose Information include:

  * if you comment on Whats-TheWord, the information you submit may be viewable to the public
  * to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or any other legal process.
  * in conjunction with a business transition, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ Information.

**Third-Party Advertising on Whats-TheWord**

Whats-TheWord allows third party advertising service vendors and advertising networks (“Third Party Vendors”) to display advertisements on Whats-TheWord. Typically, these third party vendors utilize cookies (defined below) first to track and collect a user’s interest-based information and then to use that information to better tailor an advertisement to that user.

Specifically:

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to Whats-TheWord.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to Whats-TheWord and/or to other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

Whats-TheWord also works with other third party vendors that use cookies to serve more targeted advertisements on Whats-TheWord. You may opt out of their use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting those vendors’ websites. These vendors include:

  * Advertising.com whose opt out page is located at <http://advertising.aol.com/privacy>

You may also opt out of these and other cookies by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

Whats-TheWord has no responsibility for the technologies, tools or practices of these third party vendors that provide advertising and related services on Whats-TheWord. This Privacy Policy does not cover any collection, use or disclosure of Information by these advertising services vendors who provide advertising and related services on Whats-TheWord. Their information gathering practices, including their policies regarding the use of cookies and other tracking technologies, are governed entirely by their own privacy policies, not this one.

**Cookies**

A cookie (otherwise known as an HTTP cookie) is a small piece of code that can be sent from a web site or banner ad and stored on a user’s web browser. The cookie stores data such as preferences, previous activity, and other information. For more information on HTTP cookies and other online advertising definitions please visit the [IAB’s web site](http://www.iab.net/insights_research/1494).

**Notices**

_Children Under 13:_ Whats-TheWord does not knowingly target advertising to, or collect information from, children under the age of 13.

_Changes to the Privacy Policy:_ Whats-TheWord reserves the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If the policy is updated, we will update the Effective Date at the bottom of the policy. Your continued use of Whats-TheWord following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. Your use of Whats-TheWord is entirely voluntary, and you may discontinue use of Whats-TheWord at any time.

_Security_ : Whats-TheWord uses all reasonable means to safeguard data against unauthorized use and theft.

_Contact Us:_ If you have questions about privacy please contact us at privacy@answersnetwork.com

**Effective date:** January 1, 2013 ****
